module.exports = {

	{name: "zSwamp",
	description: "He's falling apart but he still has room to love",
	image: "url",
	locationName: "Swamp",
	locationImage: "url",
	questions: [
		{
			question: "How are you today?",
			responses: [
				{response: "Great", value: 10},
				{response: "None of your business", value: -20}
			]
		},
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		},
		
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		}

	]
	},
	{	name: "zBeach",
	description: "He's falling apart but he still has room to love",
	image: "url",
	locationName: "Beach",
	locationImage: "url",
	questions: [
		{
			question: "How are you today?",
			responses: [
				{response: "Great", value: 10},
				{response: "None of your business", value: -20}
			]
		},
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		},
		
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		}

	]},
	{
	name: "zSnow",
	description: "He's falling apart but he still has room to love",
	image: "url",
	locationName: "Snow",
	locationImage: "url",
	questions: [
		{
			question: "How are you today?",
			responses: [
				{response: "Great", value: 10},
				{response: "None of your business", value: -20}
			]
		},
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		},
		
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		}

	]
	},
	{name: "zMansion",
	description: "He's falling apart but he still has room to love",
	image: "url",
	locationName: "Mansion",
	locationImage: "url",
	questions: [
		{
			question: "How are you today?",
			responses: [
				{response: "Great", value: 10},
				{response: "None of your business", value: -20}
			]
		},
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		},
		
		{
			question: "How do you feel about zombies?",
			responses: [
				{response: "I hate them", value: 10},
				{response: "They're awesome!", value: -20}
			]	
		}

	]}
}